Chaitanya Gupta, Computer Science Engineering Undergraduate

7042124510, chaitanyagupta01@gmail.com

LINKS	<u>Linkedin</u>			
PROFILE	Passionate individual skilled in experimental design, execution and results tracking for field research activities and studies. Monitored industry changes and reviewed lectures and assignments to identify and implement appropriate syllabus revisions. Communicates complex information in simple and concise format.			
EXPERIENCE				
Jan 2021 — Present	Promotions and Marketing Head at Dream Merchants VIT, Dream Merchants VIT			Vellore
	Dream Merchants is a club which intends to provide a platform for the future leaders and corporate captains. Our objective is to develop an interest among the individuals in the field of finance, business at entrepreneurship. Our aim is to provide opportunities to students to explore a career in Finance and Trade understanding the relationship between business and economic disciplines.			ce, business and
Feb 2021 — Mar 2021	Data Science and Business Analytics Intern, SPARKS Foundation			
	"Prediction Model using Supervised ML"			
	The Task involved prediction of percentage of student based on the no. of study hours usin			g linear regression.
Feb 2020	Volunteer, Riviera			Vellore
	Riviera is the Annual International Sports and Cultural Carnival of the Vellore Institute of Technology. It is an International 4-day event that consists of sports competitions, social and cultural events along with concerts. Wa part of the Publicity and Marketing International team and handled International Student operations.			
EDUCATION				
Jul 2019 — Present	Bachelors, Vellore Institute of Technology Vello			Vellore
	Computer Science Engineering with Specialization in Information Security			
May 2019	High School, Mount Carmel School			Delhi
SKILLS	Python	Experienced	Knowledge of MS Office	Expert
	C++	Experienced	Ethical Hacking	Skillful
	Web Development	Skillful	Data Analysis	Experienced
	Machine Learning	Skillful	Cloud	Skillful
CERTIFICATIONS				
	AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner, Amazon			
	AWS Certified Cloud P	ractitioner, Amazon		
	AWS Certified Cloud P			
		nd Complexity, UC		